optimalpayments.com 2019-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Paysafe

###  Privacy Notice 

This Privacy Notice was last amended on 24/05/2018

This notice applies to Paysafe Group Limited and its group companies, which sometimes use trading names including Paysafe, Paysafecard, Payolution, Skrill and Neteller (together “Paysafe” or “we” or “our”).

This notice shows our commitment to protect your privacy rights and sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. It applies to:

  * the website/portal features and services provided to you when you visit our websites, portals or our payment panels our clients may use on their websites;
  * when you apply to use and/or use Paysafe’s products and services (including any loyalty or reward schemes, whether points-based or otherwise (“Loyalty” or “Promotion”);
  * your use of software including terminals, mobile and desktop applications provided by Paysafe; and
  * email, other electronic messages including SMS, telephone, web chat, website/portal and other communications between you and Paysafe.  

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

Paysafe takes a “layered approach” to explaining its privacy practices, as recommended by regulators. This means that we endeavour to initially provide you with the key privacy information in the form of this “short form” privacy notice. Should you wish to view the comprehensive privacy notice, you can click here. Contact us details are provided at the end of the notice, for feedback or any privacy enquiries you may have.

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**  
You may provide some information to us, for example when you enquire for or make an application for the Paysafe Services, register to use and/or use any Paysafe Services, by filling in forms on one of our websites, participating in one of our events or by corresponding with by us phone, e-mail, web chat or otherwise. We may collect some of it through automatic means, for example by using cookies when you visit our websites. Read our Cookie Policy to know more. We may also obtain data about you from third parties, like credit reference and fraud prevention agencies.

**USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**  
We use information we collect about you to provide you with the products we offer, to notify you about changes to our products and to improve our products. We also use this information to provide you with information about other products we or selected third parties offer which are similar to the ones you have used or enquired about or we think may be of interest to you. If you use one of our financial products, we will also use your information to assess your financial situation and to try to identify and prosecute possible frauds.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
We will not disclose your personal data to anyone except as described in this notice.  
We may share your personal information with any company in the Paysafe Group Limited group of companies.

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with the products we offer, including service providers, credit reference agencies and financial institutions.  We may also share your personal information with third parties to prevent crime and reduce risk, if required to do so by law, where we deem it appropriate to do so, to respond to legal process or to protect the rights or property of Paysafe, our customers or others.

**WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND DATA SECURITY**  
The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, stored at and processed by recipients located in destinations outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). These countries may have data protection standards that are different to (and, in some cases, lower than) those in which you reside. We will take all steps necessary to ensure that the recipients will use and protect your information in the same secure way that we do.

If we have given you (or if you have chosen) a password, access code or any other secure means or access or authentication which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential and complying with our instructions. You must not share credentials with anyone else, and you authorise Paysafe to act upon instructions and information from any person that enters your credentials.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site, unless you are communicating with us through a secure channel that we have provided. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**YOUR RIGHTS**  
Where applicable, you may have certain rights under data protection legislation, including the right to access, correct, update or delete your personal information; object to or restrict its processing; request to transfer certain of your personal information to another service provider (so called, data portability); or to revoke any consent you have given.

However, please note that there are exceptions to those rights. For the full explanation of the rights available, please refer to the comprehensive privacy notice.

**AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING**  
Automated decisions mean that a decision concerning you is made automatically on the basis of a computer determination (using software algorithms), without our human review. 

For example, we use automated decisions to complete a credit assessment on you when you apply to financial services of Paysafe, or to carry out anti-fraud checks on the transactions you perform. However, if you are in the European Union, you have the right to object the automated decision and have it manually reviewed based also on information that you can provide.

You can contact us at the details below to exercise your right.

**LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING**  
We will process your personal information only when we have one of the following ground:

  * On the basis of your consent, for example to send you marketing messages;
  * Where necessary to enter into a contract with you and perform our obligations under that contract;
  * Where we have a legitimate interest, subject to such processing not overriding your own rights and freedoms;
  * Where we have a legal obligation to collect your personal information or otherwise needs your Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person; or
  * Exceptionally, when necessary in the public interest, for example when law enforcement agencies request information to investigate a crime.  

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE**  
Any changes we may make to our privacy notice in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy notice.

**CONTACT US**  
All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed. If you wish to exercise any of your rights or receive further information as to the applicable Paysafe group companies to which this notice applies, you should write to the address below, marked FAO Privacy Department or [Contact Us](https://www.paysafe.com/support/).

Paysafe’s Data Protection Officer is as stated below and can be contacted via the Contact us link above or at the address below:

Mr Derek A Wynne

Paysafe, Floor 27, 25 Canada Square, London, E17 4AU
